Go

Copy & Paste a Product URL 

 RUN REPORT

Copy & Paste a Product URL 

 RUN REPORT

Privacy Policy
==============

_April 28th, 2016_

This Site is operated by:

Review Honesty, Inc. A Nevada Corporation

PO BOX 29502 #61891

Las Vegas NV, 89126

[\[email protected\]](https://reviewmeta.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

This Privacy Policy explains how this Site treats “personal information” that we gather from visitors and how we use it. Please, also read our Terms of Use for better understanding of Privacy Policy.

“Personal Information” is information that is personally identifiable like a name, e-mail address, or other information that we can reasonably link to such information.

1. What We Gather and How We Do It
    * In order to better provide you with our numerous services, we collect two types of information about our users: Personally Identifiable Information and Nonpersonally Identifiable Information. Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience while using our site.
    * Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as registering for a membership, ordering a product or service, submitting content and/or posting content in discussion forums or other public areas, entering a contest or sweepstakes, filling out a survey, or sending us feedback, we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities, elect to engage in these activities, however, we may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including zip code), email address, and other personal identifying information. When ordering products or services on the site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number. Depending upon the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.
    * Nonpersonally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. We gather certain information about you based upon where you visit on our site in several ways. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. This information may include the Web site’s Uniform Resource Locator (“URL”) that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address. A URL is the global address of documents and other resources on the World Wide Web. An IP address is an identifier for a computer or device on a Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol (“TCP/IP”) network, such as the World Wide Web. Networks like the Web use the TCP/IP protocol to route information based on the IP address of the destination. In other words, an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web, allowing web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers require IP addresses in order for users to communicate on the Internet.
    * Our Web server automatically collects information from a visitor’s computer and browser, including their internet protocol (IP) address and cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is sent to your Web browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. When you visit this Site, a cookie may be sent to your computer. You can control whether or not you want to accept cookies by adjusting the settings of your browser.
    * Third party vendors may use cookies to serve ads based on prior visits to this website. No personal information is collected by these cookies. You can opt out of third party vendor’s cookies at any time by visiting this page: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt\_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)
    * We do not collect any Personally Identifiable Information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. You provide certain Personally Identifiable Information to us when you: (a) register for our services and register your email address with us; (b) enter sweepstakes or contests sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) sign up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) send email messages, submit forms or transmit other information by telephone or letter; or (e) submit your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our site. We may also collect information from you at other points on our site that state that such information is being collected.
    * Our site uses Google Analytics to help us gather and analyze traffic to our site.  You can read more about the [Google Analytics data policies here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en).

2. How We Use the Information We Gather
    * We do not distribute or sell your personal information. We do not send you advertisements and we do not share your email address with anyone.
    * We may use the personal information that visitors provide us to respond to correspondence, contact them regarding their membership account, improve the content of our Site, and for informational or other developmental purposes.
    * If you subscribe to our newsletter, we will send you a weekly email, and not share your information with anyone else. You may unsubscribe from the newsletter anytime you want.
    * When you post a review, all the information you submit is displayed for anyone to read. This may include the bio that you submit, your username, comments, age, location, or any other information that you input into our system. We will not share your date of birth, email address or password with anyone. Those are all items which we will never publicly display.
    * We may use the information collected by our Web servers to analyze traffic patterns, record session information, store visitors’ preferences and identify sources of web traffic to the Site.
    * We may also use the information we collect to investigate, prevent or take action against suspected illegal activities, problems with this Site, or as required by law. We may use the information for legal proceedings, such as responding to subpoenas, court orders, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. In the event that our company or its assets are acquired by or merged with a third party, the information collected by our Site may be one of the assets transferred.
    * Occasionally we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful.
    * We may also provide Nonpersonally Identifiable Information about our customers’ sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to third party advertisers, but these statistics do not include any Personally Identifiable Information.

3. Sites Not Covered by this Policy. Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Other sites accessible through our site have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Please consult each site’s privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. Additionally, other companies which place advertising on our site may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising through the use of cookies. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect.
4. Security Measures. Our web hosting company uses industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer information exchanged with our Site. Our web hosting company has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our Site. Although we believe that our web hosting company provides appropriate security measures, we are not responsible for the practices, actions or inactions of that company.
5. Changes to this Policy. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time, and without advance warning, by updating this page. You are bound by all such revisions and should, therefore, review the Privacy Policy every time you visit this Site.
6. Terms of Use. Nothing herein waives, limits or in any way modifies our Terms of Use. This Site is not directed to, nor does it knowingly collect any personal information from children under 18. If a child who we know to be under age 18 sends personal information to us online, we will only use that information to respond directly to that child, notify parents or seek parental consent.
7. Opt Out Rights. By using this website you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and collection and use of your personal information byReviewMeta.com as specified above. If at any time after visiting the Site, you change your mind about receiving information from the Site or sharing your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy, you may request an opt out, by contacting us at: [\[email protected\]](https://reviewmeta.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Questions or Additional Information ~ If you have any questions about this Policy, or if you would like additional information, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://reviewmeta.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

*   
    
    Newsletter
    ==========

    accept permissions to continue...
    
     Yes, I consent to my personal data being used to receive useful content for my brand, VIP event invites, and more information from ReviewMeta. You can unsubscribe anytime. For more details, please review our [Privacy Policy](https://reviewmeta.com/blog/privacy/)
    
    Leave this field empty if you're human: 
    
*   
    
    Popular Posts
    =============
    
    * [
        
        More than just Fake Reviews: Why ReviewMeta.com detects all types of bias](https://reviewmeta.com/blog/more-than-just-fake-reviews-why-reviewmeta-com-detects-all-types-of-bias/)
    * [
        
        How Accurate is ReviewMeta.com?](https://reviewmeta.com/blog/how-accurate-is-reviewmeta-com/)
    * [
        
        Amazon Review Hijacking – How to Spot Sellers that are Recycling Reviews on Amazon](https://reviewmeta.com/blog/amazon-review-hijacking/)
    * [
        
        ReviewMeta.com Press & Media](https://reviewmeta.com/blog/press/)
    * [
        
        Streamline your experience with the ReviewMeta Browser Extension!](https://reviewmeta.com/blog/extensions/)

###### Quicklinks

###### Newsletter Signup

 Yes, I consent to my personal data being used to receive useful content for my brand, VIP event invites, and more information from ReviewMeta. You can unsubscribe anytime. For more details, please review our [Privacy Policy](https://reviewmeta.com/blog/privacy/) Please, accept permissions to continue...

1. Follow us on...
2. [](https://www.facebook.com/reviewmeta)
3. [](https://twitter.com/reviewmeta)
